Guide to the Katherine S. Dreier Papers / Societe Anonyme Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Société Anonyme: Correspondence, 1917-1950; Series VII; 1.4; (4 boxes)
  - Rumsey, Susan Fiske, 1920, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 2195)
  - "S" general, 1920-35, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 2196)
  - S. W. Frankel Advertising Agency, Inc., 1927 (Box 85, Folder 2197)
    See also: Art News
  - Schoenfeld, Flora, 1921, 1923, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 2198)
  - Simon, Melly, 1923-25 (Box 85, Folder 2199)
  - Spingarn, Amy E., 1925 (Box 85, Folder 2200)
  - Spurr, B. M.
    See: Box 33, folder 964
  - Steinway & Sons, 1925 Apr 9 (Box 85, Folder 2201)
  - Stella, Antonio, 1921-25, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 2202)
  - Stella, Joseph
    See: Box 33, folders 967-968
  - Stettheimer, Ettie, 1920 (Box 85, Folder 2203)
  - Stieglitz, Alfred
    See: Box 33, folders 970-971
  - Stransky, Josef, 1921 Mar 20 (Box 85, Folder 2204)
  - Sullivan, Mary
    See: Box 34, folder 981
  - Sun (New York, N.Y.), 1920-27 (Box 85, Folder 2205)
    See also: Oversize, box 130, folder 2873
  - Swain, Mary K., 1922-24 (Box 85, Folder 2206)
  - "T" general, 1920-41, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 2207)
  - Taylor, Henry Fitch, 1920-23 (Box 85, Folder 2208)
  - Thayer, Scofield, 1920-25 (Box 85, Folder 2209)
    See also: Box 10, folder 297
  - Thompson, Leverett (Mrs.), 1923, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 2210)
  - Thompson, William Boyce, 1920, 1923 (Box 85, Folder 2211)
  - Tofel, Jennings, 1921-47 (Box 85, Folder 2212)
  - Townley, Chambers & Clare, 1948 (Box 85, Folder 2213)
  - Tyler, Helen, 1920, 1923, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 2214)
  - Typon Reflex Paper Co.
    See: Polygraphic Company of America
  - Valmier, Georges, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 2215)
  - Valori Plastici, 1919-20, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 2216)
  - Van Everen, Jay, 1920-27, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 2217)
  - Vanity Fair, 1920 (Box 85, Folder 2218)
  - Veltin School (New York, N.Y.), 1920 Oct 6 (Box 85, Folder 2219)
  - "W" general, 1920-27, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 2220)
  - Walls, Franklin Jasper, 1920-25 (Box 85, Folder 2221)
  - Werblow, David
  - Wescott, Glenway, 1920 (Box 86, Folder 2222)
  - Wesselhoeft, Mary F., 1923-26 (Box 86, Folder 2223)
  - Whitney, Harry Payne (Mrs.), 1920-25 (Box 86, Folder 2224)
  - Wilcox, Urquhart, 1921 (Box 86, Folder 2225)
  - Wilhelm, Richard
    See: Box 37, folder 1103
  - Williams, Eleanor Troy
    See: Box 37, folder 1104
  - Worcester, Charles H.
    See: Box 37, folder 1116
  - World (New York, N.Y.), 1920-25, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 2226)
  - Wurzweiler, Fiffi, 1923, 1925, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 2227)
  - Wyer, Raymond
    See: Raymond Henniker-Heaton
  - Zorach, William, 1923-27 (Box 86, Folder 2228)
  - Charlotte, 1925, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 2229)
  - Unidentified, 1920, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 2230)
  - Open letters to members, 1921-28, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 2231-2232)
- Société Anonyme: Public Programs, 1920-1950; Series VIII; 1.6; (4 boxes)
  Series VIII, Société Anonyme: Public Programs, is organized into four subseries: Exhibitions, Lectures, Music, and Other.
  - EXHIBITIONS
    - Ephemera & Printed Material
      - 19 East 47th Street, New York (N.Y.)
        - 1st, 1920 Apr 30-Jun 15. Flyer (Box 87, Folder 2233)
        - 2nd, 1920 Jun 17-Aug 1. Flyer and press release (Box 87, Folder 2234)
        - 3rd, 1920 Aug 2-Sep 11. Flyer (Box 87, Folder 2235)
        - 4th, 1920 Sep 13-Oct 23. Flyer (Box 87, Folder 2236)
        - 5th, 1920 Nov 1-Dec 15. Flyer, drafts, typescript carbon and printed (Box 87, Folder 2237)
        - 6th, 1920 Dec 15-1921 Feb 1. Flyer, drafts, typescript carbon and printed (Box 87, Folder 2238)
        - 7th, 1921 Feb 1-Mar 15. Flyer, drafts, typescript carbon and printed (Box 87, Folder 2239)
        - 8th, 1921 Mar 15-Apr 12. Flyer, drafts, typescript carbon and printed (Box 87, Folder 2240)
        - 9th, 1921 Apr 16-May 15. Flyer (Box 87, Folder 2241)
        - 10th, 1921 May 16-Jun 15. Flyer (Box 87, Folder 2242)
        - "Reopening of their Gallery," 1922 Dec 16. Announcement (Box 87, Folder 2243)
        - 12th, 1923 Jan 10-Feb 5. Flyer (Box 87, Folder 2244)
        - 13th, 1923 Feb 5. Flyer, drafts, typescript carbon and printed (Box 87, Folder 2245)
        - 14th, 1923 Feb 23-Mar 22. Flyer (Box 87, Folder 2246)
        - 15th, 1923 Mar 23-May 4. Flyer (Box 87, Folder 2247)
      - 44 West 57th Street, New York (N.Y.)
        - 16th, 1924 Jan 7-Feb 7. Flyer, clipping (Box 87, Folder 2248)
        - 17th, 1924 Feb 13-Mar 6. Flyer, clipping (Box 87, Folder 2249)
        - 19th, 1924 Mar 31-Apr 12. Flyer (Box 87, Folder 2250)
        - 20th, 1924 Apr 16-29. Flyer (Box 87, Folder 2251)
        - "Exhibition of Paintings by David Burliuk," 1924 Mar 8-29
          - Invitation to meet Mr. & Mrs. David Burliuk, 1924 Mar 8, typescript, corrected (Box 87, Folder 2252)
          - Catalog, [1924]
      - Addison Gallery of American Art. "4 Painters," 1937 Feb. Clippings (Box 87, Folder 2253)
      - Albright Art Gallery (Buffalo, N.Y.). "An International Exhibition Illustrating the Most Recent Development in Abstract Art," 1931 Feb 18-Mar 8
        - Catalog, [1931] (Box 87, Folder 2254)
        - Clippings, 1931
      - Albright Art Gallery (Buffalo, N.Y.). "The International Exhibition of Modern Art," 1927 Feb 25-Mar 20
        - Catalog, [1927] (Box 87, Folder 2255)
        - Clipping, 1927 Feb 26
      - American Woman's Association. "From Impressionism to Abstraction: 13 Women Painters," 1934 Nov 14-Dec 8
        - Catalog, [1934] (Box 87, Folder 2256)
        - Clippings, 1934-35
      - Anderson Galleries. "Fernand Léger," 1925 Nov 16-28
        See also: Box 74, folder 1922
        - Notes, holograph, typescript, and carbon, [1925] (Box 87, Folder 2257)
        - Flyer, typescript carbon, corrected, [1925]
        - Advertisement, proof, [1925]
        - Invitation to opening, typescript carbon and printed, 1925 Nov 16
        - Catalog, typescript, corrected and printed, [1925] (Box 87, Folder 2258)
        - List of publications to which book was sent, typescript carbon, corrected, 1925 Nov 10
        - List of clippings, typescript and carbon, corrected, 1926, n.d.
      - Anderson Galleries. "The International Exhibition of Modern Art," 1927 Jan 25- Feb 5
        - Announcement, [1927] (Box 87, Folder 2259-2260)
        - Catalog, proof and printed, [1927]
        - Clipping, 1927 Jan 29
      - Art Institute of Chicago. "A Century of Progress: Exhibition of Paintings and Sculptures," 1933 Jun 1-Nov 1. Catalog (Box 87, Folder 2261)
      - Arts Club of Chicago. "4 Painters," 1937 Feb 5-27
        - Catalog, [1937] (Box 87, Folder 2262)
        - Clippings, 1937
      - Arts Club of Chicago. "Exhibition of Paintings by Marcel Duchamp," 1937 Feb 5-27. Catalog (Box 87, Folder 2263)
      - Arts Council of the City of New York. "A Small Intimate Exhibition," 1928 Feb 20-Mar 3
        - List of paintings, holograph, [1928] (Box 87, Folder 2264)
        - Announcement, [1928]
      - Baltimore Museum of Art. "An Exhibition of Modern French Art," 1925 Jan 9-Feb 1. Catalog (Box 87, Folder 2265)
      - Bennington College. "4 Painters," 1936 Oct 15-Nov 9
        See: Box 74, folder 1923
      - Brooklyn Museum. "Exhibition of Paintings and Drawings by the Late Walter Shirlaw and a Group of His Pupils," 1929 Dec 2-1930 Jan 2
        - Invitation to meet Ruth St. Denis and Ted Shawn, 1930 Jan 3 (Box 88, Folder 2266)
        - "List of Pictures to be Exhibited," typescript carbon, corrected, [1929]
        - Press releases, [1929]
        - Catalog, [1929] (Box 88, Folder 2267-2268)
      - Brooklyn Museum. "Exhibition of Russian Painting and Sculpture," 1923 Jan 23- Mar 4. Catalog (Box 88, Folder 2269)
      - Brooklyn Museum. "International Exhibition of Modern Art," 1926 Nov 19- 1927 Jan 9
        - Notes, holograph, typescript and carbon, corrected, 1926, n.d. (Box 88, Folder 2270)
        - Tags (unused), [1926] (Box 88, Folder 2271)
        - Catalog, [1926] (Box 88, Folder 2271)
        - Clippings, 1926-27 (Box 88, Folder 2272)
      - Brummer Gallery (New York, N.Y.). "Contemporary Paintings," 1929 Nov 30- Dec 13. Clipping, 1929 Dec 8 (Box 88, Folder 2273)
      - Buchholz Gallery (New York, N.Y.). "Paul Klee," 1940 Oct 9-Nov 2. Catalog (Box 88, Folder 2274)
      - Carnegie Institute. "Lauren Ford: Paintings, Drawings and Etchings," 1939 Mar 16-Apr 30. Catalog (Box 88, Folder 2275)
      - Columbia University. "Exhibition of Paintings," 1938 Feb 28-Mar 24. Invitation; notes, holograph (Box 88, Folder 2276)
      - Daniel Gallery. "Heinrich Campendonk," 1925 Mar 23-Apr 4
        - Invitation, drafts, typescript and printed, [1925] (Box 88, Folder 2277)
        - Checklist, drafts, typescript and carbon, corrected, [1925]
        - Catalog, [1925]
        - Clipping, [1925]
      - Delphic Studios. "4 Painters: Albers, Dreier, Drewes, Kelpe," 1936 Nov 23- Dec 5
        - Announcement, [1936] (Box 88, Folder 2278)
        - Catalog, [1936]
        - Clippings, 1936, n.d.
      - George Walter Vincent Smith Art Museum. "Some New Forms of Beauty," 1939 Nov 9-Dec 17
        See also: Box 74, folder 1927
        - Catalog, [1939] (Box 88, Folder 2279-2280)
        - Clippings, 1939, n.d.
      - Kaiser Wilhelm Museum Krefeld. "Dorothea Adelheid Dreier," 1929 Dec. Catalog (Box 88, Folder 2281)
      - Kingore Galleries (New York, N.Y.). "The Archipenko Exhibition," 1924 Jan 20-Feb 9. Catalog (Box 88, Folder 2282)
      - MacDowell Club. 1922 Apr 24 May 8. Clipping, 1922 Apr 30 (Box 88, Folder 2283)
      - Macy's. "Exposition of Art in Trade at Macy's," 1927 May 2-7. Catalog (Box 88, Folder 2284)
      - Michigan Art Institute. "A Collection of Works by the Modernist-Expressionist Groups," 1923 Aug 31-Sep 9. Catalog (Box 88, Folder 2285)
      - Museum of Fine Arts (Springfield, Mass.). "4 Painters," 1937 Jan 1-15. Clippings (Box 89, Folder 2286)
      - Museum of Fine Arts (Springfield, Mass.). "French Painting: Cézanne to the Present," 1935 Dec 7-1936 Jan 5. Catalog (Box 89, Folder 2287)
      - Museum of Fine Arts (Springfield, Mass.). "In Freedom's Search," 1950 Jan 15-Feb 19
        - Catalog, [1950] (Box 89, Folder 2288)
        - Clippings, 1950, n.d.
      - Museum of Fine Arts (Springfield, Mass.). "Modern German Art," 1939 Jan 10-30. Catalog (Box 89, Folder 2289)
      - Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.). "Cubism and Abstract Art," 1936 Mar 2- Apr 19. Clipping (Box 89, Folder 2290)
      - Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.). "Fantastic Art, Dada, Surrealism," 1936 Dec 7-1937 Jan 17. Invitation to opening, 1936 Dec 8 (Box 89, Folder 2291)
      - Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.). "German Painting and Sculpture," 1931 Mar 13-Apr 26. Catalog (Box 89, Folder 2292)
      - New School for Social Research (New York, N.Y.). "In honor of the opening of the new building," 66 W. 12th Street," 1931 Jan 1-Feb 10
        - Flyer, [1931]
          See: Oversize, box 120, folder 2843
        - Announcement, [1931] (Box 89, Folder 2293)
        - Notes, holograph and typescript, corrected, [1931]
        - Clippings, 1930-31, n.d.
      - Nierendorf Gallery. "An Exhibition of Contrasts," 1939 Mar 28-Apr 8. Catalog (Box 89, Folder 2294)
      - Rand School of Social Science. 35th, 1930 Oct 7-Nov 8
        - Flyer, [1930] (Box 89, Folder 2295)
        - Clippings, 1930
      - Rand School of Social Science. 36th, 1930 Nov 10-Dec 10
        - Flyer, [1930] (Box 89, Folder 2296)
        - Clippings, 1930
      - Rand School of Social Science. 37th, 1931 Jan 5-Mar 16. Flyer, drafts, typescript and carbon, corrected, and printed (Box 89, Folder 2297)
        See also: Oversize, box 120, folder 2844
      - Rand School of Social Science. 43rd, 1931 Mar 16-Apr 30 (Box 89, Folder 2298)
      - Rand School of Social Science. Exhibitions, 1930-31
        - Announcements, drafts, holograph and typescript, corrected, [1930] (Box 89, Folder 2299)
        - Clippings, 1930-31
      - San Francisco Museum of Art. "4 Painters," 1937 Apr-May. Clippings (Box 89, Folder 2300)
      - University of Chicago Renaissance Society. "A Selection of Works by Twentieth Century Artists," 1934 Jun 20-Aug 20. Catalog (Box 89, Folder 2301)
      - University of Chicago Renaissance Society. "Some Modern Primitives: International Exhibition of Paintings and Prints," 1931 Jul 2-Aug 16. Catalog (Box 89, Folder 2302)
      - University of Wisconsin. "Third Wisconsin Salon of Art," 1936 Nov 11- Dec 7. Catalog (Box 89, Folder 2303)
      - Vassar College. "Exhibitions of Paintings by Modern Masters of Spain, Germany, France, Russia, Italy, Belgium and America," 1923 Apr 4-May 12. Catalog (Box 89, Folder 2304)
      - Wadsworth Atheneum. "4 Painters," 1936 Dec 7-28. Clippings, 1936 Dec 26 (Box 89, Folder 2305)
      - Wadsworth Atheneum. "Impressionism to Abstraction: 13 Women Painters," 1934 Dec 13-1935 Jan 30. Catalog (Box 89, Folder 2306)
      - Wadsworth Atheneum. "Newer Super- Realism," 1931 Nov. Catalog (Box 89, Folder 2307)
        Includes "Notes on Surrealisme," brochure.
      - Wadsworth Atheneum. "Some New Forms of Beauty," 1940 Jan 4-Feb 4. Catalog (Box 89, Folder 2308)
      - Wilmington Society of the Fine Arts (Wilmington, Del.). "Exhibition of Russian Painting and Sculpture: Realism to Surrealism," 1932 Jan 11-31. Catalog (Box 89, Folder 2309)
      - Women's University Club. 1931 Feb. Clippings (Box 89, Folder 2310)
      - Worcester Art Museum. "Exhibition of Paintings by Members of the Société Anonyme," 1921 Nov 3-Dec 5
        - Catalog, [1921] (Box 89, Folder 2311)
        - Clipping, [1921]
      - Unidentified
        - Flyers, drafts, holograph and typescript carbon, corrected (Box 89, Folder 2312)
    - Other
      - "Artists Exhibited by the Société Anonyme, Inc.," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2313)
      - "Aufstellung," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2314)
      - "List of German Prints of the Ernst Arnold Gallery of Dresden Arranged by Société Anonyme, Inc.," typescript carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2315)
      - Artwork owned by the Société Anonyme. Lists, holograph, typescript, and carbon, corrected (Box 90, Folder 2316)
      - "Collection of the Société Anonyme, Museum of Modern Art: 1920. Held in Trust: Trustees: Marcel Duchamp and Katherine S. Dreier," drafts, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 90, Folder 2317-2320)
      - Exhibition space. Notes, holograph, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2321)
      - Exhibition space at 19 East 47th Street, New York (N.Y.)
        - Sketch, n.d.
          See: Oversize, box 120, folder 2845
        - Blueprint, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2322)
      - Log book, holograph, 1920-28 (Box 90, Folder 2323)
  - LECTURES
    - Announcements
      - "Its Lectures and Exhibition, Winter 1930-31" (2 types) (Box 90, Folder 2324)
    - Invitations
      - "Jacques Villon," by Walter Pach, at 19 East 47th Street, New York (N.Y.), Dec 28, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2325)
      - "Lecture on Modern Art", Apr 30, n.d.
      - "Primitive Art Contrasted with the Modern," by Alexander Goldenweiser, at 19 East 47th Street, New York (N.Y.), Mar 15, 22, 29
    - Other
      - [List of lectures organized by SA, 1920-42], drafts, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 90, Folder 2326)
  - MUSIC
    - International Symphony. Introductory concert, 1930 Feb 9. Clippings, finances, correspondence, invitation, 1930, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2327)
    - "Modern Russian Music and Dances," at 44 West 57th Street, New York (N.Y.). Program, 1924 Mar 8 (Box 90, Folder 2328)
    - "Three Lectures with Piano Recital," by Frances de Villa Ball, at 44 West 57th Street, New York (N.Y.), 1925 Mar-Apr
      - Invitation, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2329)
      - Program, n.d.
  - OTHER
    - Brochure Quarterly, 1928 Jul (Box 90, Folder 2330)
      Includes loose cut for page 14; advertisement, drafts, holograph and printed; clippings.
    - Scrapbook [#1], 1920-24
      See: Oversize, box 129, folder 2872
    - Scrapbook [#1]. Loose material from, 1921, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2331)
    - Scrapbook [#2], 1921-30
      See: Oversize, box 130, folder 2873
    - Scrapbook [#2]. Loose material from, 1927, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2332)
    - Stationery, general (unused), n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2333)
    - Stationery, Reference Library (unused), drafts, n.d.
    - Envelopes, 3 types (unused), n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2334)
    - Motto, typescript and carbon (Box 90, Folder 2335)
- Société Anonyme: Business Records, 1920-1950; Series IX; 1; (3 boxes)
  Series IX. Société Anonyme: Business Records, is organized into five subseries: Finances, Legal Materials, Membership, Structure/Management of the Society, and Transfer to Yale University.
  - FINANCES
    - Account statements, 1920-27, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2336-2338)
    - Bank of New York and Trust Company. Check book, 1927-30 (Box 91, Folder 2339)
    - New York (N.Y.). Dept. of Finance. Certificate authorizing collection of sales tax, 1935 Jan 14 (Box 91, Folder 2340)
    - Security Insurance Company of New Haven. Policy, 1931
      See: Oversize, box 120, folder 2846
  - LEGAL MATERIALS
    - By-Laws, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2341)
    - Amendments to the By-Laws, [1920] (Box 91, Folder 2342)
    - Certificate of Incorporation, drafts, holograph and typescript, 1920 Apr 29 (Box 91, Folder 2343)
  - MEMBERSHIP
    - Lists of members, 1924, 1926, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2344)
    - Lists of members to whom publications were sent, 1926, 1928, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2345)
    - Brochure, drafts and printed version (Box 91, Folder 2346)
    - Brochure for reopening of membership, notes, drafts, and printed version, [1948?] (Box 91, Folder 2347)
    - Consent form, 2 types (unused), n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2348)
    - Card (unused), n.d. (Box 92, Folder 2349)
    - Card, $5 (unused), n.d.
    - Card, $10 (unused), n.d.
    - Cards
      - Ackerman, Phyllis, 1923 Jan 1 (Box 92, Folder 2350)
      - Aldis, Arthur T., 1923 Jan 1
      - Barksdale, Ethel du Pont (2 copies), 1920 Jul 17
      - Boix, 1920 Sep 25
      - Bourgeois, Stephan, 1921, 1923
      - Brinton, Christian, 1924 Jan
      - Bruguière, Francis Joseph, 1921 Feb 2
      - Cane, Florence, 1923 Jan 1
      - Cheney, Sheldon, 1920 Oct 25
      - Daniel, Charles H., 1920 Jun 10
      - De Liagre, Alfred, 1924 Feb
      - Denks, F., 1921 Mar 12
      - Denniston, Martha Durand, 1923 Jan 1
      - Dick, Gladys R., 1920, 1921
      - Dodge, Philip Lyndon, 1924 Jan
      - Dreier, H. Edward, 1922, 1924 (Box 92, Folder 2351)
      - Dreier, Katherine S., n.d.
      - Dreier, Mary E., 1923 Jan 1
      - Duchamp, Marcel, Sr., 1920, 1923
      - Duchamp, Marcel, 1923 Mar
      - Eilshemius, Louis M., 1923, 1924
      - Erbslöh, Rudolf, 1924 Jan
      - Gallatin, A. E., 1921, 1923
      - Greene, Belle da Costa, 1923 Apr
      - Gross, Paul, 1923 Jan
      - Hare, Meredith, 1922 Apr 7
      - Hartley, Marsden, 1921 Feb 16
      - Harvey, Dorothy Dudley, 1921 Mar 19
      - Heinecke, William, 1923 Apr
      - Huntington, Archer Milton, 1921 May 7 (Box 92, Folder 2352)
      - Huntington, Margaret W., 1924 Jan
      - Iaccaci, Thayer (Mrs.), 1921 Oct 30
      - Kandinsky, Wassily, 1923 Mar
      - Kauffmann, Carrie, 1924 Jan
      - Kennerley, Helen A., 1920 Dec 6
      - King, Georgiana Goddard, 1923 Apr
      - King, Kunpah, 1922
      - Knoblauch, Mary, 1921, 1923
      - Lavat, C. M., 1924 Jan
      - Lemon, Courtenay, 1923 Mar
      - Lewisohn, Sam A., 1923 Mar
      - Loving, Pierre, 1923 Mar
      - Ludington, Wright S., 1924 Jan 14
      - McBride, Henry, 1923 Mar
      - Macgowan, Kenneth, 1921 Mar 26
      - McLaren, Andrew R., 1921, 1923
      - Mooney, Edmund L., 1924 Jan
      - Nadelman, Elie, 1923 Jan 1 (Box 92, Folder 2353)
      - Nathans, Gwendolyn, 1921 Jul 24
      - Neumann, J. B., 1924 Jan
      - O'Brien, Daniel, 1923 Mar 15
      - O'Day, Caroline, 1923, 1924
      - Putnam, Frances F., 1920, 1923
      - Ray, Man, 1921 Feb 16
      - Robins, Gretchen, 1923 Jan 1
      - Ronchi, Nino, 1923 Apr
      - Rosenfeld, Paul L., 1923 Jan 1
      - Schoenfeld, Flora, 1923 Apr
      - Schurz, Carl (Mrs.), 1920 Oct 8
      - Shoop, Max, 1922
      - Simon, Melly, 1923 Jan 1
      - Stella, Joseph, 1923 Mar
      - Stettheimer, Carrie W., 1921 Feb 16
      - Stettheimer, Florence, 1920 Jun
      - Stransky, Josef, 1921 Mar 19 (Box 92, Folder 2354)
      - Sullivan, Mary, 1923 May 19
      - Taylor, Henry Fitch, 1922 Apr 2
      - Thayer, Scofield, 1923 Jan 1
      - Thayer, Mabel, 1923 May 23
      - Thompson, Leverett (Mrs.), 1923 Apr
      - Thompson, William Boyce, 1920 Nov 27
      - Tofel, Jennings, 1923 Apr
      - Tyler, Helen, 1920 May 29
      - Tyrrell, Henry, 1921 Jan 29
      - Untermyer, Minnie, 1920 Dec 14
      - Van Everen, Jay, 1923 Mar
      - Walkowitz, Abraham, 1924 Jan 1
      - Walls, Franklin Jasper, 1924 Jan
      - Weinrich, Agnes, 1923 Jan 1
      - Werblow, Henry, 1923 Jan 1
      - Werblow, Robert, 1923 Jan 1
      - Wilhelm, Richard, 1922
      - Zorach, William, 1920, 1923
  - STRUCTURE/MANAGEMENT OF THE SOCIETY
    - Committees and officers. Lists, typescript and carbon, 1920 (Box 93, Folder 2355)
    - Directions for the Custodian, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 93, Folder 2356)
    - Meeting minutes, holograph, typescript, and carbon, corrected, 1920-46, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 2357-2359)
    - Mission statements, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 93, Folder 2360)
    - Publications of the SA. Lists, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 93, Folder 2361)
    - Publicity. Notes on, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 93, Folder 2362)
    - Reference Library contents. Lists, holograph, typescript, and carbon, corrected (Box 93, Folder 2363)
    - Report (1920-21)
      - Typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 2364)
      - Photographs, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 2365-2367)
        See also: Oversize, box 120, folder 2847
  - TRANSFER TO YALE UNIVERSITY
    - Notes and material regarding transfer, 1941-43, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 2368-2369)
    - Announcement of gift and of exhibit, 1941, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 2370)
    - Poster for exhibition, Jan 14-Feb 22, at Yale University Art Gallery (3 copies), n.d.
      See: Oversize, box 120, folder 2848
    - Invitation regarding dissolution of Société Anonyme, draft, typescript carbon and printed, 1950, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 2371)
      Includes place cards and list of guests.
    - Announcement regarding catalog, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 2372)
    - Clippings regarding announcement, exhibitions, and catalog, 1941-50, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 2373)
- Société Anonyme: Subject Files about Artists, 1872-1952; Series X; 9.2; (24 boxes)
  Series X, Société Anonyme: Subject Files about Artists, is arranged alphabetically by name. The content of the file for each artist is arranged in the following order (where present): questionnaire, notes, manuscripts, catalogs and pamphlets, clippings, photographs of artist, and photographs of artwork. Additional photographs of artists and their artwork may be found in Series V, Katherine S. Dreier: Photographs and Artwork.
  - Alajalov, Constantine, 1925-49, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 2374-2376)
  - Albers, Josef, 1936-49, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 2377-2379)
  - Annot, 1934-49, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 2380-2381)
    See also: Oversize, box 120, folder 2849
  - Archipenko, Alexander, 1919-43, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 2382-2390)
  - Arp, Jean, 1944, 1949, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 2391-2393)
  - Balla, Giacomo, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 2394)
  - Barlach, Ernst, 1949, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 2395)
  - Barnes, Charles E., 1949, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 2396)
  - Bauer, Rudolf, 1949, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 2397)
  - Baumeister, Willi, 1922-49, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 2398-2402)
  - Bergmann-Michel, Ella, 1950, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 2403)
  - Biederman, Charles Joseph, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 2404)
  - Bloch, Albert, 1949, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 2405)
  - Boccioni, Umberto, 1949, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 2406)